(Raj:)Son of a bitch.
(Raj:)You're a sucky friend, you know that?
(Raj:)A sucky, sucky friend.
(Howard:)What was I supposed to do?
She gave me that come-hither look.
If she gave you any look at all,
it was a you-suck look.
(Howard:)I would've caught up to her
if I hadn't pulled a hammy.
(Raj:)Oh, please, you weigh 80 pounds,
you don't have a hammy.
(Leonard:)So Penny doesn't want me around her
friends. I embarrass her. What else?
(Sheldon:)Well, her actions could be
out of concern for your feelings.
(Sheldon:)Perhaps she's excluded you
from these gatherings...
(Sheldon:)...because she's scouting for a new mate
and doesn't wanna do it in front of you.
(Leonard:)Oh, how kind of her.
(Sheldon:)Agreed. Most primates don't show
that sort of discretion.
(Sheldon:)A female bonobo will copulate with
a new male in front of the old one...
(Sheldon:)...without so much as a,
"How do you do?"
You always do this. Ditch me
for a woman you don't have a shot with.